A Guide to the Papers of the Institute of Public Affairs, University of Virginia, 1927-1953
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Correspondance and Miscellaneous Records (Box 54-145)
  - Round Table: "Special Conference of the League of Virginia Municipalities"
    - Harold I. Baumes [1934] (Box 81)
    - Seth Burnley [1934] (Box 81)
    - Harold S. Buttenheim [1934] (Box 81)
    - Program of the Conference [1934] (Box 81)
    - Laurence V. Smith [1934] (Box 81)
    - William A. Smith [1934] (Box 81)
    - Morton L. Wallerstein [1934] (Box 81)
  - Round Table: "Special Conference on State Planning"
    - Charles J. Calrow [1934] (Box 81)
    - Jacob Crane [1934] (Box 81)
    - Charles W. Eliot, II [1934] (Box 81)
    - Program of Conference [1934] (Box 81)
  - L. S. Rowe 1934 (Box 81)
  - Speakers Invited 1934 (Box 81)
  - Speakers Who Declined Invitations 1934 (Box 81)
  - Lowell Thomas 1934 (Box 81)
  - R. Gray Williams 1934 (Box 81)
  - Attendance--Acceptances and Regrets 1935 (Box 81)
  - Biographies 1935 (Box 81)
  - Budget [1935] (Box 81)
  - Hon. Harry F. Byrd 1935 (Box 81)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace [1935] (Box 81)
  - E. I. Carruthers, Bursar [1935] (Box 81)
  - Duplicate Vouchers [1935] (Box 81)
  - Evening Speakers
    - Hon. Allen W. Berkley 1935 (Box 82)
    - William B. Bell 1935 (Box 82)
    - Evening Speakers-Invited 1935 (Box 82)
    - Dr. Charles O. Hardy 1935 (Box 82)
    - Colonel LeRoy Hodges 1935 (Box 82)
    - Hon. Rush D. Holt 1935 (Box 82)
    - Hon. Cordell Hull 1935 (Box 82)
    - Gen. Hugh S. Johnson 1935 (Box 82)
    - Miss Katharine Lenroot 1935 (Box 82)
    - Hon. George C. Peery 1935 (Box 82)
    - Mrs. William Dick Sporborg 1935 (Box 82)
    - Hon. James W. Wadsworth 1935 (Box 82)
    - Hon. Sumner Welles 1935 (Box 82)
  - Governor's Delegates 1935 (Box 82)
  - Miscellaneous "A-W" 1935, 14 folders (Box 82)
  - Dr. Raymond Moley 1935 (Box 82)
  - Hon. R. Walton Moore 1935 (Box 82)
  - President John Lloyd Newcomb 1935 (Box 82)
  - Past Contributors [1935] (Box 82)
  - Gov. George C. Peery 1935 (Box 82)
  - Registration in Round Tables 1935 (Box 82)
  - Report on Institute to Committee from the Rector and Board of Visitors [1935] (Box 82)
  - Robert E. Lee Memorial Foundation, Inc. 1935 (Box 82)
  - Rotary Club of Christiansburg [1935] (Box 83)
  - Rotary Club of Lynchburg [1935] (Box 83)
  - Rotary Club of Richlands [1935] (Box 83)
  - Rotary Club of Waverly [1935] (Box 83)
  - Rotary International [1935] (Box 83)
  - Rotary International-Governor's Monthly Letters [1935] (Box 83)
  - Round Table: "American-German Relations"
    - Dr. Frederick E. Auhagen, Leader [1935] (Box 83)
    - Virginius Dabney, Esq. [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. K. G. Frank [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. Henry G. Hodges [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. Walter A. Knittle [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. Frederick K. Kruger [1935] (Box 83)
    - Rabbi Morris Lazaron [1935] (Box 83)
    - Henry Albert Phillips, Esq. [1935] (Box 83)
    - Henry A. Pochmann, Esq. [1935] (Box 83)
    - Program [1935] (Box 83)
    - Ernst Schmitz, Esq. [1935] (Box 83)
    - George N. Shuster [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. H. F. Simon [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. John A. Walz [1935] (Box 83)
    - Miss Mildred Wertheimer [1935] (Box 83)
  - Round Table: "The Church in a Changing World"
    - Rev. John McDowell, Leader [1935] (Box 83)
    - Rev. Albert D. Belden [1935] (Box 83)
    - Rev. William Adams Brown [1935] (Box 83)
    - Rabbi Edward N. Calisch [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. Everett R. Clinchy [1935] (Box 83)
    - Rev. Don Frank Fenn [1935] (Box 83)
    - Rev. Cameron Parker Hall [1935] (Box 83)
    - Mrs. Elizabeth Ireland [1935] (Box 83)
    - Rabbi Edward L. Israel [1935] (Box 83)
    - Rev. R. A. McGowan [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. Henry W. McLaughlin [1935] (Box 83)
    - Program [1935] (Box 83)
    - Rev. John Elliott Ross [1935] (Box 83)
  - Round Table: "The Constitution and the New Deal"
    - Demarest Lloyd, Leader [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. Neil Carothers [1935] (Box 83)
    - Raoul Desvernine, Esq. [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. James Hart [1935] (Box 83)
    - David J. Lewis [1935] (Box 83)
    - Mrs. Helen H. Miller [1935] (Box 83)
    - W. C. Murphy, Jr. [1935] (Box 83)
    - J. Howard Pew [1935] (Box 83)
    - C. W. Putnam [1935] (Box 83)
    - Hon. Fred J. Sisson [1935] (Box 83)
    - Program [1935] (Box 83)
    - Nicolas Roosevelt [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. Walter E. Spahr [1935] (Box 83)
    - Hon. Albert E. Stephen [1935] (Box 83)
  - Round Table: "Contemporary Educational Issues"
    - George B. Zehmer, Leader [1935] (Box 83)
    - Thomas G. Bennett [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. Scott M. Buchanan [1935] (Box 83)
    - J. L. B. Buck [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. George S. Counts [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. Wayne Dennis [1935] (Box 83)
    - Miss Jane Dickey [1935] (Box 83)
    - Miss Mary B. Duncan [1935] (Box 83)
    - Miss Jeffries Heinrich [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. H. M. Johnson [1935] (Box 83)
    - Dr. Isaac L. Kandel [1935] (Box 83)
    - Miss Leila Mechlin [1935] (Box 83)
    - Miss Clara Saunders [1935] (Box 83)
    - Program [1935] (Box 83)
  - Round Table: "Cooperation and Conflict Across the Pacific"
    - Grover Clark, Leader [1935] (Box 84)
    - Commander Archer M. R. Allen [1935] (Box 84)
    - Adrian J. Barnouw [1935] (Box 84)
    - Miss Pearl S. Buck [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Paul H. Clyde [1935] (Box 84)
    - Frederick V. Field [1935] (Box 84)
    - Keener C. Frazer [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Clifford C. Hubbard [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. William Johnstone [1935] (Box 84)
    - Donald C. McDonald [1935] (Box 84)
    - C. K. Moser [1935] (Box 84)
    - Program [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Harold Scott Quigley [1935] (Box 84)
    - Speakers Invited [1935] (Box 84)
    - Richard J. Walsh [1935] (Box 84)
  - Round Table: "Economic Security"
    - Dr. Eveline M. Burns, Leader [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Barbara Armstrong [1935] (Box 84)
    - Jacob Baker, Esq. [1935] (Box 84)
    - Mrs. Geline MacD. Bowman [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Douglas Brown [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Ewan Clague [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. J. C. Flippin [1935] (Box 84)
    - Miss Emma H. Gunther [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Joseph P. Harris [1935] (Box 84)
    - Arthur W. James, Esq. [1935] (Box 84)
    - Albert Linton, Esq. [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Broadus Mitchell [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. William Ogburn [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Raymond Pinchbeck [1935] (Box 84)
    - Program [1935] (Box 84)
    - Mrs. Eudora Ramsay Richardson [1935] (Box 84)
    - [1935] Miss Winifred Wilson (Box 84)
  - Round Table: "European Relations: Rebuilding Peace"
    - Dr. J. Anton de Haas, Leader [1935] (Box 84)
    - Rev. Paul D. Bowden [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Karl Brandt [1935] (Box 84)
    - Charles K. Brown [1935] (Box 84)
    - Rev. Paul D. Bowden [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Gerhard Colm [1935] (Box 84)
    - John D. Crowle, Jr. [1935] (Box 84)
    - Monsieur Gerreau Dombasle [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Alvin H. Hanson [1935] (Box 84)
    - Edward Jenkins, Esq. [1935] (Box 84)
    - Edward R. Johnson [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. William E. Linglbach [1935] (Box 84)
    - Dr. Denys P. Myers [1935] (Box 84)
    - William McC. Paxton [1935] (Box 84)
    - Program [1935] (Box 84)
    - Speakers-Invited [1935] (Box 84)
    - L. H. Timmons [1935] (Box 84)
    - David J. Saposs [1935] (Box 84)
    - William S. Swingel, Esq. [1935] (Box 84)
  - Round Table: "Latin America: International, Economic, and Social Developments"
    - Dr. Charles W. Hackett, Leader [1935] (Box 85)
    - Senor Dr. Licenciado Ramón Beteta [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. W. W. Cumberland [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. Carlos G. Davila [1935] (Box 85)
    - John S. de Wilde, Esq. [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. Henry F. Grady [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. Leland H. Jenks [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. R. A. McGowan [1935] (Box 85)
    - Peter Molyneaux [1935] (Box 85)
    - Program [1935] (Box 85)
    - Invited Speakers [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. Joseph F. Thorning [1935] (Box 85)
    - Mrs. Helena Hill Weed [1935] (Box 85)
  - Round Table: "The Place of Religion in Character Education"
    - Rev. Minor C. Miller, Leader [1935] (Box 85)
    - Rabbi Edward N. Calisch [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. Steward G. Cole [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. Paul Eddy [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. D. W. Peters [1935] (Box 85)
    - Program [1935] (Box 85)
    - Speakers Invited [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. Karl Stoltz [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. James V. Thompson [1935] (Box 85)
  - Round Table: "Problems of Reconstruction in the Light of History"
    - Dr. Robert McElroy, Leader [1935] (Box 85)
    - Colonel Henry Breckinridge [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. Francis W. Coker [1935] (Box 85)
    - John Daniels [1935] (Box 85)
    - Clark M. Eichelberger, Esq. [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. A. J. Hettinger, Jr. [1935] (Box 85)
    - Clarence King [1935] (Box 85)
    - John L. Lewis [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. Ellis P. Oberholtzer [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. Ernest Minor Patterson [1935] (Box 85)
    - Program [1935] (Box 85)
    - Alexander Sacks [1935] (Box 85)
  - Round Table: "The Significance of American Membership in the International Labour Office"
    - Spencer Miller Jr., Leader [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. John B. Andrews [1935] (Box 85)
    - Samuel McCune Lindsay [1935] (Box 85)
    - Isador Lubin [1935] (Box 85)
    - Leifur Magnusson [1935] (Box 85)
    - Program [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. Leland Rex Robinson [1935] (Box 85)
    - Dr. James T. Shotwell [1935] (Box 85)
    - Thomas G. Spates [1935] (Box 85)
  - Round Table: "Taxation for Prosperity"
    - Dr. Thomas H. Reed, Leader [1935] (Box 86)
    - R. C. Atkinson [1935] (Box 86)
    - Daniel Bloomfield [1935] (Box 86)
    - Harold S. Buttenheim [1935] (Box 86)
    - Arnold Frye [1935] (Box 86)
    - Dr. Jens P. Jensen [1935] (Box 86)
    - Hon. Henry S. Long [1935] (Box 86)
    - Hon. Joseph McGoldrick [1935] (Box 86)
    - Harry McCullan, Esq. [1935] (Box 86)
    - Dr. James W. Martin [1935] (Box 86)
    - Program [1935] (Box 86)
    - Noel Sargent [1935] (Box 86)
    - Prof. Carl Shoup [1935] (Box 86)
    - Herbert D. Simpson [1935] (Box 86)
    - John F. Sly, Esq. [1935] (Box 86)
    - A. H. Stone, Esq. [1935] (Box 86)
    - Speakers--Invited [1935] (Box 86)
    - The Royal Institute of International Affairs 1935 (Box 86)
    - Jouett Shouse 1935 (Box 86)
    - Speakers Invited 1935 (Box 86)
  - Special Conferences: Cooperative Education Association, General Federation of Women's Clubs
    - Mrs. Fred M. Alexander [1935] (Box 86)
    - Dr. J. H. Montgomery [1935] (Box 86)
  - Statements of Expenses 1935-1950 (Box 86)
  - Lowell Thomas 1935 (Box 86)
  - Veterans' Associations 1935 (Box 86)
  - The Academy of Sciences and Fine Arts of the United States of America 1936 (Box 86)
  - Biographical Data 1936 (Box 86)
  - Budget 1936 (Box 86)
  - Hon. Harry Flood Byrd 1936 (Box 86)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace 1936 (Box 86)
  - Harry Clemons 1936 (Box 86)
  - Contributions 1936 (Box 86)
  - Colonel Manton Davis 1936 (Box 86)
  - Governor's Delegates 1936 (Box 86)
  - Raoul E. Desvernine 1936 (Box 86)
  - Editorial Comments on Institute 1936 (Box 86)
  - Entertainment 1936 (Box 86)
  - J. Fred Essary 1936 (Box 86)
  - Evening Lectures
    - Winthrop Williams Aldrich 1936 (Box 87)
    - Hon. Hiram Bingham 1936 (Box 87)
    - William O. Douglas 1936 (Box 87)
    - Dr. Alexander Vincent Dye 1936 (Box 87)
    - Charles R. Gay 1936 (Box 87)
    - Dr. Garrard Glenn 1936 (Box 87)
    - John Temple Graves, II 1936 (Box 87)
    - Walter Hampden 1936 (Box 87)
    - Hon. Harold Ickes 1936 (Box 87)
    - T. Z. Koo 1936 (Box 87)
    - Hon. Herman Langworthy 1936 (Box 87)
    - Rev. John McDowell, D.D. 1936 (Box 87)
    - Dr. Robert McElroy 1936 (Box 87)
    - Hon. Stanley F. Reed 1936 (Box 87)
    - Speakers Invited 1936 (Box 87)
    - Henry W. Taft 1936 (Box 87)
    - Dr. Mary E. Woolley 1936 (Box 87)
    - Dr. Barbara Frances Wootton 1936 (Box 87)
  - Expense Accounts-Paid 1936 (Box 87)
  - Federation of American Women's Clubs Overseas [1936] (Box 87)
  - Foreign Policy Association [1936] (Box 87)
  - General Education Board [1936] (Box 87)
  - R. M. Hanes--Correspondence 1936 (Box 87)
  - Mailing List 1936 (Box 87)
  - Dr. Charles G. Maphis 1936 (Box 87)
  - Dr. Maphis' Letter to Virginius Dabney, Esq. 1936 (Box 87)
  - Memberships 1936 (Box 87)
  - Miscellaneous "B-W" 1936, 15 folders (Box 87)
  - Hon. R. Walton Moore 1936 (Box 88)
  - Raymond Moley, Esq. 1936 (Box 88)
  - Dr. John Lloyd Newcomb [1936] (Box 88)
  - Open Forum
    - F. W. Allport 1936 (Box 88)
    - Carl F. Arnold, Esq. 1936 (Box 88)
    - John Fahey, Esq. 1936 (Box 88)
    - Roger Baldwin, Esq. 1936 (Box 88)
    - Prof. Arthur W. Bromage 1936 (Box 88)
    - Louis G. Caldwell 1936 (Box 88)
    - Dr. Frank Ongley Darvall 1936 (Box 88)
    - Dr. Charles G. Fenwick 1936 (Box 88)
    - Elisha Hanson, Esq. 1936 (Box 88)
    - Gen. James G. Harbord 1936 (Box 88)
    - Dr. Herman S. Hettinger 1936 (Box 88)
    - Ben Howe 1936 (Box 88)
    - Dr. Alexander Meiklejohn 1936 (Box 88)
    - Gorham Munson 1936 (Box 88)
    - Colonel Theodore Roosevelt, Jr. 1936 (Box 88)
    - Franklyn Waltman 1936 (Box 88)
    - Frederic A. Willis 1936 (Box 88)
    - Speakers Invited 1936 (Box 88)
    - Speakers Who Declined Invitation 1936 (Box 88)
    - Program 1936 (Box 88)
  - Photographs 1936 (Box 88)
  - Radio Broadcast 1936, July 17 (Box 88)
  - Receipts [1936] (Box 88)
  - Hon. Franklin D. Roosevelt 1936 (Box 88)
  - Rotary International [1936] (Box 88)
  - Round Table: "The American Political Scene"
    - Spencer Miller Jr., Leader 1936 (Box 88)
    - Alfred Bingham, Esq 1936 (Box 88)
    - Earl Browder 1936 (Box 88)
    - Dr. T. N. Carver 1936 (Box 88)
    - Hon. John Dickinson 1936 (Box 88)
    - Dr. Mordecai Ezekiel 1936 (Box 88)
    - William Hoster, Esq. 1936 (Box 88)
    - Ben Howe, Esq. 1936 (Box 88)
    - Dr. Benjamin B. Kendrick 1936 (Box 88)
    - Herman Langworthy 1936 (Box 88)
    - Dr. Samuel McCune Lindsay 1936 (Box 88)
    - Harold Loeb 1936 (Box 88)
    - Mrs. Thomas McAllister 1936 (Box 88)
    - Raymond Gram Swing, Esq. 1936 (Box 88)
    - Speakers Declined 1936 (Box 88)
    - Dr. Willam Lonsdale Taylor 1936 (Box 88)
    - Hon. Norman Thomas 1936 (Box 88)
    - Howard Y. Williams, Esq. 1936 (Box 88)
    - Mrs. George Wyeth 1936 (Box 88)
    - Miscellaneous 1936 (Box 88)
    - Program 1936 (Box 88)
  - Round Table: "Changing Asia"
    - Grover Clark, Leader [1936] (Box 89)
    - Mrs. Kate Barnes [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. H. Belshaw [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. Elizabeth Boody [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. Ben Dorfman [1936] (Box 89)
    - W. I. Holland, Esq. [1936] (Box 89)
    - Younghill Kang, Esq. [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. T. Z. Koo [1936] (Box 89)
    - Mrs. T. D. Macmillan [1936] (Box 89)
    - M. Matsuo, Esq. [1936] (Box 89)
    - T. S. Miyakawa [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. Frederick W. Norwood [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. Cyrus Peake [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. R. T. Shields [1936] (Box 89)
    - Program [1936] (Box 89)
  - Round Table: "The Church and the Problem of Democracy"
    - Rev. John McDowell, Leader [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. Samuel McCrea Cavert [1936] (Box 89)
    - Hon. Frederick M. Davenport [1936] (Box 89)
    - Rev. Henry Smith Leiper [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. Samuel McCune Lindsay [1936] (Box 89)
    - Miss Elizabeth Longwell [1936] (Box 89)
    - Rev. John A. MacCallum [1936] (Box 89)
    - Rev. R. A. McGowan [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. Henry W. McLaughlin [1936] (Box 89)
    - Rev. Minor C. Miller [1936] (Box 89)
    - Lovell H. Parker, Esq. [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. Charles J. Turck [1936] (Box 89)
    - Miscellaneous [1936] (Box 89)
    - Program [1936] (Box 89)
  - Round Table: "Current Problems in Our Latin American Relations"
    - Dr. Dana G. Munro, Leader [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. William Wilson Cumberland [1936] (Box 89)
    - Henry L. Deimel [1936] (Box 89)
    - Prof. Henry Gratton Doyle [1936] (Box 89)
    - W. E. Dunn [1936] (Box 89)
    - Ernest Galarza, Esq. [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. Julio Garcia-Diaz [1936] (Box 89)
    - John B. Glenn [1936] (Box 89)
    - Donald Heath [1936] (Box 89)
    - Robert H. Patchin, Esq. [1936] (Box 89)
    - Dr. Adrian Recinos [1936] (Box 89)
    - William A. Reid, Esq. [1936] (Box 89)
    - Judge Otto Schoenrich [1936] (Box 89)
    - Miscellaneous [1936] (Box 89)
    - Speakers Who Declined Invitation [1936] (Box 89)
  - Round Table: "Government and Business"
    - John G. Paine Esq., Leader [1936] (Box 90)
    - Lyle A. Brookover [1936] (Box 90)
    - John Calvin Brown [1936] (Box 90)
    - Maj. Richard S. Buck [1936] (Box 90)
    - Siegfried Hartman [1936] (Box 90)
    - Robert S. Henry [1936] (Box 90)
    - A. J. Hettinger [1936] (Box 90)
    - Hon. Sullivan Jones [1936] (Box 90)
    - Hon. Basil Manly [1936] (Box 90)
    - E. L. Oliver [1936] (Box 90)
    - Rev. Willfrid Parsons [1936] (Box 90)
    - W. L. Schurz, Esq. [1936] (Box 90)
    - Wylie R. Wright [1936] (Box 90)
    - Speakers Invited [1936] (Box 90)
    - Speakers Who Declined Invitation [1936] (Box 90)
  - Round Table: "International Good Will"
    - Dr. Robert McElroy, Leader [1936] (Box 90)
    - P. H. W. Almy [1936] (Box 90)
    - Rev. Paul D. Bowden [1936] (Box 90)
    - Spencer Brodney [1936] (Box 90)
    - Charles K. Brown [1936] (Box 90)
    - Frederick R. Coudert [1936] (Box 90)
    - John D. Crowle, Jr. [1936] (Box 90)
    - Dr. William Wilson Cumberland [1936] (Box 90)
    - Henry S. Cumming [1936] (Box 90)
    - Gerald John Ross Delafield [1936] (Box 90)
    - Dr. Frank P. Graham [1936] (Box 90)
    - Dr. Herbert Sherman Houston [1936] (Box 90)
    - Edward R. Johnson [1936] (Box 90)
    - William A. Luke, Jr. [1936] (Box 90)
    - J. E. Mallonee [1936] (Box 90)
    - William B. Murphy [1936] (Box 90)
    - Ernest Minor Patterson [1936] (Box 90)
    - William McC. Paxton [1936] (Box 90)
    - Hugo E. Prager, Esq. [1936] (Box 90)
    - Alexander Sachs [1936] (Box 90)
    - Speakers Invited [1936] (Box 90)
    - Speakers Invited [1936] (Box 90)
    - Speakers Who Declined Invitation [1936] (Box 90)
    - Miscellaneous [1936] (Box 90)
    - Program [1936] (Box 90)
  - Round Table: "Local Government"
    - Prof. Arthur W. Bomage, Leader [1936] (Box 91)
    - Frank Bane, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - Roy S. Braden, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - Maj. Charles J. Calrow [1936] (Box 91)
    - Edward W. Carter, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - Willard F. Day [1936] (Box 91)
    - Hon. Thomas C. Desmond [1936] (Box 91)
    - Maxwell A. DeVoe, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - John N. Edy [1936] (Box 91)
    - Hon. C. R. Erdman [1936] (Box 91)
    - Prof. Cullen B. Gosnell [1936] (Box 91)
    - H. A. Haden, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - R. W. B. Hart [1936] (Box 91)
    - J. R. Hayden, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - Arthur W. James [1936] (Box 91)
    - Howard P. Jones, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - Prof. John W. Manning [1936] (Box 91)
    - Prof. John W. Manning [1936] (Box 91)
    - James W. Martin, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - C. H. Morrisett [1936] (Box 91)
    - Prof. Frank W. Prescott [1936] (Box 91)
    - Oliver C. Short [1936] (Box 91)
    - Prof. Earl L. Shoup [1936] (Box 91)
    - John F. Sly, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - John F. Sly, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - Dr. George W. Spicer [1936] (Box 91)
    - Raymond Uhl [1936] (Box 91)
    - Morton L. Wallerstein [1936] (Box 91)
    - Delegates [1936] (Box 91)
    - Miscellaneous [1936] (Box 91)
    - Speakers Declined [1936] (Box 91)
    - Program [1936] (Box 91)
  - Round Table: "Public Opinion in a Democracy"
    - Dr. Herman S. Hettinger, Leader [1936] (Box 91)
    - F. W. Allport, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - Jerome D. Barnum, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - Edward L. Bernays, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - William Ludlow Chenery [1936] (Box 91)
    - Dr. Nathaniel P. Clough [1936] (Box 91)
    - Lambdin Kay, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - Dr. Clyde King [1936] (Box 91)
    - Dr. Harold D. Lasswell [1936]
    - Philip G. Loucks, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - Alexander Markey, Esq. [1936] (Box 91)
    - Felix Morley [1936] (Box 91)
    - Felix Morley [1936] (Box 91)
    - Program [1936] (Box 91)
  - Round Table: "The Stock Exchange"
    - Program [1936] (Box 92)
    - Speakers Who Declined the Invitation [1936] (Box 92)
  - Speakers on Program
    - Arthur A. Ballantine [1936] (Box 92)
    - Dr. W. W. Cumberland [1936] (Box 92)
    - Colby M. Chester, Esq. [1936] (Box 92)
    - Dr. W. Randolph Burgess [1936] (Box 92)
    - William O. Douglas, Esq. [1936] (Box 92)
    - Robert M. Hanes, Leader [1936] (Box 92)
    - K. C. Holgate, Esq. [1936] (Box 92)
    - Charles Klem [1936] (Box 92)
    - Eugene Lokey [1936] (Box 92)
    - Matthew Woll, Esq. [1936] (Box 92)
    - Charles H. Meyer, Esq. [1936] (Box 92)
    - George V. McLaughlin, Esq. [1936] (Box 92)
    - Godfrey N. Nelson, Esq. [1936] (Box 92)
    - Edmund Platt [1936] (Box 92)
    - Dr. F. D. G. Ribble [1936] (Box 92)
    - Leland Rex Robinson, Esq. [1936] (Box 92)
    - Orrin G. Wood, Esq. [1936] (Box 92)
  - Special Conference: "The Cooperative Education Association"
    - W. H. Bristow, Leader [1936] (Box 92)
    - Mrs. S. C. Cox [1936] (Box 92)
    - Dr. J. H. Montgomery [1936] (Box 92)
    - Program [1936] (Box 92)
  - Special Conference: "The Emergency and Long-Run Aims of Education"
    - Dr. Scott M. Buchanan, Leader [1936] (Box 92)
    - John Clarke Adams [1936] (Box 92)
    - Arthur Fletcher, Esq. [1936] (Box 92)
    - Dr. William H. McHugh [1936] (Box 92)
    - Dr. Alexander Meikeljohn [1936] (Box 92)
    - Nathaniel Peffer, Esq. [1936] (Box 92)
    - Gerold van Minden [1936] (Box 92)
  - Special Conference: "National Society United Daughters of 1812"
    - Mrs. William Armistead Porter 1936 July (Box 92)
    - Mrs. Willis Hitzing 1936 July (Box 92)
    - Miscellaneous 1936 July (Box 92)
  - Special Conference: "Power Age Economics"
    - Gorham Munson, Leader 1936 July (Box 92)
    - Allen T. Gwathmey 1936 July (Box 92)
    - Paul Hampden 1936 July (Box 92)
    - Edward F. Harvey, Esq. 1936 July (Box 92)
    - James Laughlin IV, Esq. 1936 July (Box 92)
    - Dr. William Carlos Williams 1936 July (Box 92)
  - Special Conference of Virginia Federation of Women's Clubs
    - Mrs. Fred M. Alexander, Leader 1936 July (Box 92)
    - Miscellaneous 1936 July (Box 92)
  - Solicitations
    - Dr. N. M. Butler 1936 (Box 92)
      8692-y
    - Irenée Dupont 1936 (Box 92)
    - Farm Foundation (H. C. Taylor) 1936 (Box 92)
    - R. V. Fleming 1936 (Box 92)
    - Form Letters 1936 (Box 92)
    - Lists 1936 (Box 92)
    - Miscellaneous 1936 (Box 92)
    - Garland Powell Peed, Treas. 1936 (Box 92)
    - Printing 1936 (Box 92)
    - Replies 1936 (Box 93)
    - Edward R. Stettinius 1936 (Box 93)
    - H. F. Strong Corporation 1936 (Box 93)
    - Henry W. Taft 1936 (Box 93)
    - Tamblyn & Brown 1936 (Box 93)
    - U. S. Commissioner of Education 1936 (Box 93)
    - Thomas J. Watson 1936 (Box 93)
    - Hon. R. Gray Williams 1936 (Box 93)
    - S. C. Williams, Jr. 1936 (Box 93)
  - United States Department of the Interior 1936 (Box 93)
  - Virginia Commission of Interracial Cooperation 1936 (Box 93)
  - Lewis C. Williams 1936 (Box 93)
  - News Releases of William H. Wranek, Jr.--Director of the University News Service 1936 (Box 93)
  - America's Town Meeting of the Air 1937 (Box 94)
  - American Red Cross 1937 (Box 94)
  - Bibliography 1937 (Box 94)
  - Biographies 1937 (Box 94)
  - The British Library of Information 1937 (Box 94)
  - Budget 1937 (Box 94)
  - Campaign for Funds
    - William J. Cameron 1937 (Box 94)
    - Raoul E. Desvernine 1937 (Box 94)
    - Irenée 1937 (Box 94)
    - Henry Ford 1937 (Box 94)
    - Contributions A--Z 1937, 2 folders (Box 94)
    - Refusals 1937 (Box 94)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace [1937] (Box 94)
  - E. I. Carruthers, Bursar [1937] (Box 94)
  - Harry Clemons-Librarian, University of Virginia 1937 (Box 94)